University Theses and Dissertations Collection UA098
Tufts Archival Research Center
University Theses and Dissertations Collection
1894 -- 2013
Tufts Archival Research Center
Graduate School of Arts and Sciences
Frances Stern Nutrition Center
Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
UA098
661.75 Linear Feet 553 boxes
8 Volumes
3 Audiovisual Object(s)
11 Digital Object(s)
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into seven series: Fletcher School dissertations; University theses and dissertations; Oversize University theses and dissertations; School of Nutrition theses; Theses containing a/v or electronic media; Deaccessioned theses; and Feinstein International Center theses.
Biographical / Historical
The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences was officially founded in 1909, more than thirty years after the first graduate degree was awarded at Tufts College.
In 1875, members of the Tufts faculty and administration approved a graduate program leading to a Master of Arts degree. The program required either one year of supervised study at Tufts, or the equivalent done away from the campus over a period of two years or more. Tufts graduates were eligible for the program, as were graduates from other schools with similar courses of study. The first MA was awarded the next spring, to a student working with the Departments of Chemistry and Physics.
Over the next few decades, interest in graduate education skyrocketed, and Tufts saw more and more students entering the program each year. In 1897, in order to meet increased demand, a Master of Sciences program was added to the graduate curriculum. Five years earlier, Tufts had established a preliminary Ph.D. program as well. The program was specifically for work in Biology and Chemistry, with other departments to be added as the faculty saw fit.
In 1892, in order to have some control over who was admitted to graduate programs, Tufts established a committee of seven faculty, led by the president. The committee picked a board of three to examine each graduate candidate and decide on their admission to the school. By the year's end, the committee was already being referred to as the graduate department.
The department finally was made official in 1903, and the office of the dean of the graduate faculty became a full time position. After the official establishment of the department, the requirements for degrees were finalized. Students were to complete thirty credit hours to receive a master's degree, and the work was to be done in one main department with related work in another.
By 1906, the size of the graduate program began to worry some members of the faculty. They were not being paid extra to teach graduate classes, which amounted to an extra course load of work for a faculty member working with as graduate student. The graduate department established a faculty committee to look into feasibility of continuing graduate education, and almost immediately the committee returned with a decision. Most of the faculty felt that graduate education was very important to make Tufts a competitive school, and also felt that the presence of graduate students increased the level of academics on campus. A year later, however, the faculty did decide to vote out the Ph.D. program. It was not reestablished until almost fifty years later.
In 1909, the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences was made official, with the administrators from the graduate department continuing in their positions. As of 2001, the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences continues to operate in numerous departments at Tufts University.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains master's theses and Ph.D. dissertations from multiple graduate schools at Tufts University. Additional Fletcher masters theses can also be found in the Fletcher School Collection. Most series contain only a container inventory. Titles to theses can be found only through the Tufts University Library catalog.
As of February 2016, theses and qualifying papers are cataloged by Tisch Library and are searchable in the Tufts University Library Catalog. DCA remains the permanent steward, but this finding aid is no longer updated with new accessions.
Separated Materials
Thesis 5897 was a non-archival duplicate copy of thesis 5776 (Vitamin B6 Status by En-Pei Isabel Chiang, 2000) and was transferred to Tisch's custody at their request on 2019-02-12 by Collections Management Archivist Adrienne Pruitt.
Curriculum and Instruction -- Student Work
- Fletcher School Dissertations, 1941 -- 2002; UA098.001; 129.85 Linear Feet; 2 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Fletcher School dissertations from 1941 to 2002. Titles to theses can be found only through the Tufts University Library catalog.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Theses, 1941F, 1943S, 1945F, 1947M, 1948P, 1948T, UA098.001.001 (Box 1)
  - Theses, 1949C, 1949N, 1950F, 1950L, 1950Lc, 1951B, 1951C, 1952A, 1952C, UA098.001.002 (Box 2)
  - Theses, 1952P, 1953F, 1953G, 1953S, 1954D, 1954E, 1954Ed, UA098.001.003 (Box 3)
  - Theses, 1954F, 1954H, 1954L, 1954M, 1954O, UA098.001.004 (Box 4)
  - Theses, 1955B, 1955G, 1955K, 1955M, 1955R, 1955S, UA098.001.005 (Box 5)
  - Theses, 1955V, 1956, 1956A, 1956E, UA098.001.006 (Box 6)
    Thesis 1956 has two volumes
  - Theses, 1956Ga, 1956Ka, 1956Ke, 1956L, 1956Lo, 1956M, 1956P, UA098.001.007 (Box 7)
  - Theses, 1956S, 1956Su, 1957C, 1957H, 1957M, 1957N, UA098.001.008 (Box 8)
  - Theses, 1957S, 1958A, 1958Ams, 1958Amst, 1958G, 1958K, 1958P, 1958R, UA098.001.009 (Box 9)
  - Theses, 1958W, 1958Wi, 1958S, 1959A, 1959As, 1959C, 1959D, 1959K, UA098.001.010 (Box 10)
  - Theses, 1959R, 1959T, 1959W, 1960B, 1960D, 1960G, UA098.001.011 (Box 11)
  - Theses, 1960S, 1960Sn, 1960St, 1960T, 1960Th, UA098.001.012 (Box 12)
    Thesis 1960St consists of two volumes
  - Theses, 1961B, 1961F, 1961M, 1961W, 1961X, 1962C, UA098.001.013 (Box 13)
  - Theses, 1962D, 1962Du, 1962G, 1962H, 1963A, 1963B, UA098.001.014 (Box 14)
  - Theses, 1963Br, 1963C, 1963J, 1963L, 1963M, 1963P, 1963Sp, UA098.001.015 (Box 15)
  - Theses, 1963Y, 1964B, 1964Bu, 1964D, 1964G, 1964H, 1963-12-01; UA098.001.016 (Box 16)
    - The Development of Political Parties in French Equatorial Africa, 1963-12-01; UA098.001.016.00001; Ballard, J. A. (John Addison), 1930-; The thesis traces the history of political organizations in French Equatorial Africa (AEF) up to 1960 and examines the failure to develop strong nationalist movements in the area. Preliminary chapters treat the historical, social and administrative background of political activity in AEF, the evolution of French African political institutions and the history of African political activity at Paris, particularly that of African parliamentary groups. The development of African elite associations and European political groups in AEF is traced from their origins after World War I through the formation of the first political parties during elections to the Constituent Assemblies of 1945-1946. Separate chapters follow in detail the development of political competition in each of the four territories of AEF from 1946 to 1957, and a short chapter summarizes developments between the creation of the first Councils of Government in 1957 and independence in 1960. A concluding section examines the origins and structure of parties and party systems in AEF. (Box 16)
      Political parties; Africa, French-speaking Equatorial--Politics and government; Africa, French-speaking Equatorial--History
  - Theses, 1964Ho, 1964K, 1964M, 1964R, 1964S, 1964St, 1964W, UA098.001.017 (Box 17)
  - Theses, 1965B, 1965C, 1965Co, 1965D, 1965G, 1965S, 1965T, UA098.001.018 (Box 18)
  - Theses, 1966Be, 1966Br, 1966G, 1966H, 1966K, 1966L, UA098.001.019 (Box 19)
  - Theses, 1966Li, 1966O,1967B, 1967G, 1967L, UA098.001.020 (Box 20)
  - Theses, 1967P, 1967R, 1967Ro, 1967S, 1967St, UA098.001.021 (Box 21)
  - Theses, 1967W, 1967Z, 1968B, 1968Cal, 1968Car, 1968Cu, 1968J, 1968M, UA098.001.022 (Box 22)
  - Theses, 1968Ma, 1968Na, 1968S, 1968Ta, 1968Th, 1968Tu, 1968W, UA098.001.023 (Box 23)
  - Theses, 1969Be, 1969Bu, 1969Co, 1969Gr, 1969Ha, 1969Hor, UA098.001.024 (Box 24)
    Thesis 1969Hor consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1969How, 1969Je, 1969Ka, 1969Mo, 1969Pl, 1969Sar, UA098.001.025 (Box 25)
  - Theses, 1969Saw, 1969Sch, 1969Ty, 1969U, 1970A, 1970Al, 1970Cr, UA098.001.026 (Box 26)
  - Theses, 1970Cro, 1970Da, 1970Ga, 1970Gar, 1970H, 1970Ho, UA098.001.027 (Box 27)
  - Theses, 1970Hou, 1970K, 1970Pe, 1970Ro, 1970Sa, 1970Sm, UA098.001.028 (Box 28)
    Thesis 1970Hou consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1970Wa, 1971A, 1971An, 1971Av, 1971Bl, 1971Br, UA098.001.029 (Box 29)
  - Theses, 1971C, 1971F, 1971H 1971J, 1971K, UA098.001.030 (Box 30)
  - Theses, 1971Ko, 1971L, 1971M, 1971Mi, 1971Mil, 1971Mu, UA098.001.031 (Box 31)
  - Theses, 1971P, 1971S, 1971T, 1971Th, 1971V, 1971W, UA098.001.032 (Box 32)
  - Theses, 1972B, 1972Be, 1972C, 1972D, 1972Du, UA098.001.033 (Box 33)
    Thesis 1972B and Thesis 1972D each consist of two volumes.
  - Theses,1972E, 1972F, 1972H, 1972K, 1972Ki, 1972L, 1972M, UA098.001.034 (Box 34)
    Thesis 1972K consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1972P, 1972R, 1972S, 1972Sm, 1972Su, 1972T, UA098.001.035 (Box 35)
    Thesis 1972P consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1972W, 1972Y, 1972Z, UA098.001.036 (Box 36)
    Thesis 1972W consists of three volumes and Thesis 1972Z consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1973A, 1973Ar, 1973B, 1973C, 1973Ca, UA098.001.037 (Box 37)
    Thesis 1973A consists of two volumes. Volume one unbound.
  - Theses, 1973D, 1973E, 1973K, 1973M, UA098.001.038 (Box 38)
    Thesis 1973D consists of two volumes and Thesis 1973M consists of three volumes.
  - Theses, 1973Mc, 1973P, 1973S, 1974A, UA098.001.039 (Box 39)
    Thesis 1973Mc consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1974B, 1974E, 1974F, 1974K, UA098.001.040 (Box 40)
    Thesis 1974B and Thesis 1974K each consist of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1974L, 1974Li, 1974M, 1974Mc, 1974N, UA098.001.041 (Box 41)
  - Theses, 1974Ni, 1974S, 1974St, 1974W, 1975C, UA098.001.042 (Box 42)
    Thesis 1974St consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1975F, 1975G, 1975H, 1975Hu, UA098.001.043 (Box 43)
    Thesis 1975Hu consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1975J, 1975O, 1975P, 1975R, 1975S, UA098.001.044 (Box 44)
    Thesis 1975J consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1975St, 1975U, 1975W, 1976A, UA098.001.045 (Box 45)
    Thesis 1976A consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1976F, 1976G, 1976H, 1976K, 1976Ko, UA098.001.046 (Box 46)
    Thesis 1976H consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1976L, 1976Le, 1976M, 1976R, UA098.001.047 (Box 47)
    Thesis 1976R consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1976Ro, 1976S, 1976St, 1976Ste, 1977B, UA098.001.048 (Box 48)
    Thesis 1976Ste consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1977Bi, 1977D, 1977Do, 1977F, 1977G, 1977J, UA098.001.049 (Box 49)
  - Theses, 1977L, 1977M, 1977Ma, 1977N, 1977No, UA098.001.050 (Box 50)
    Thesis 1977L consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1977P, 1977Po, 1977R, 1977S, 1977Y, 1978A, UA098.001.051 (Box 51)
  - Theses, 1978BL, 1978C, 1978F, 1978G, 1978I, UA098.001.052 (Box 52)
    Thesis 1978G consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1978K, 1978Ka, 1978Kr, 1978L, 1978M, 1978P, UA098.001.053 (Box 53)
  - Theses, 1978R, 1978S, 1979A, 1979B, 1979Bu, 1979C, UA098.001.054 (Box 54)
  - Theses, 1979Ca, 1979Co, 1979D, 1979E, UA098.001.055 (Box 55)
    Thesis 1979Ca consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1979F, 1979Fo, 1979Fr, 1979J, UA098.001.056 (Box 56)
    Theses 1979Fr and 1979J each consist of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1979M, 1979S, 1979T, UA098.001.057 (Box 57)
    Theses 1979S and 1979T each consist of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1979Th, 1980D, 1980E, 1980F, 1980Fr, 1980H, UA098.001.058 (Box 58)
  - Theses, 1980Ho, 1980M, 1980Ma, 1980Mc, 1980R, 1980Ra, UA098.001.059 (Box 59)
    Thesis 1980M consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1980Rh, 1980Ro, 1980S, 1980St, 1980T, 1980Tu, UA098.001.060 (Box 60)
    Thesis 1980Ro consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1980W, 1981A, 1981B, 1981E, UA098.001.061 (Box 61)
    Theses 1981B and 1981E each consist of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1981K, 1981Le, 1981Li, 1981Ma, 1981My, UA098.001.062 (Box 62)
    Theses 1981K and 1981My each consist of volumes.
  - Theses, 1981Ra, 1981Ry, 1981Sp, 1981Str, 1981Stu, UA098.001.063 (Box 63)
    Thesis 1981Ry consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1981Ve, 1981Vl, 1981Wa, 1981We, 1982Ca, 1980-09; UA098.001.064 (Box 64)
    Thesis 1981Ve consists of two volumes.
    - The Australian purchase of three United States guided missile destroyers: A study of the defense aspect of Australian-American relations, 1980-09; UA098.001.064.00001; Wallace, Roy Neil; The objectives of this dissertation are to a. contribute to the body of scholarly knowledge on Australia and, in particular, its political and national security situation; b. identify the causes and effects of the transfer of a modern combatant ship to a nation which had not previously had United States ships in its fleet; c. improve the understanding of security aspects of alliance relationships. (Box 64)
      Australia--Defenses; Australia--Foreign relations--United States; Military assistance, American--Australia
  - Theses, 1982Cr, 1982D, 1982F, 1982L, UA098.001.065 (Box 65)
    Theses 1982D and 1982L each consist of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1982S, 1982Tu, 1982W, 1982Z, 1983Gr, 1983Ka, UA098.001.066 (Box 66)
    Thesis 1982W consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1983Ma, 1983Mi, 1983No, 1983Ra, 1983Si, 1984Bl, UA098.001.067 (Box 67)
  - Theses, 1984Bo, 1984C, 1984Cy, 1984G, 1984Go, UA098.001.068 (Box 68)
  - Theses, 1984K, 1984Ka, 1984Ke, 1984Ki, UA098.001.069 (Box 69)
    Thesis 1984Ke consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1984Ku, 1984L, 1984M, 1984Mc, 1984Mcc, 1984N, UA098.001.070 (Box 70)
  - Theses, 1984No, 1984S, 1984T, 1985Al, 1985Br, 1985He, 1984-04; UA098.001.071 (Box 71)
    - Marine Technology Transfer and the Law of the Sea, 1984-04; UA098.001.071.00001; Stavridis, James G. (Box 71)
      On 10 December 1982, a signing ceremony was held for the United Nations Convention on the Law of the Sea (UNCLOS) in Montego Bay, Jamaica. The comprehensive Law of the Sea Treaty was signed by delegates from 117 countries, and the document represented over nine years of difficult negotiations conducted by nearly 3,000 representatives and negotiators. The Treaty is a comprehensive effort to regulate the world's oceans, and includes provisions on a wide range of issues, including territorial seas, the continental shelf, the high seas, marine scientific research, exploitation of the deep seabed, straits passage (for commercial shipping and warships), fishing rights, and technology transfer. The accord creates several new international organizations l including mechanisms for regulation of deep seabed mining, dispute resolution, and other ocean affairs. The United States, along with several other major Western industrial countries, has indicated unwillingness to ratify the Treaty due to concerns over the deep seabed regime in general and the technology transfer sub-regime in particular. This dissertation focuses on two primary research questions. The first is: How important was the issue of marine technology transfer to the emerging ocean regime? The second is: In what way can the Treaty be improved or refined in order to improve the possibility of full Western participation in the agreement?
      theses
  - Theses, 1985Is, 1985K, 1985Lu, 1985Me, UA098.001.072 (Box 72)
  - Theses, 1985Mir, 1985Pr, 1985Sa, 1985Ti, 1985Ze, UA098.001.073 (Box 73)
    Thesis 1985Mir consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1986A, 1986B, 1986C, 1986D, 1986Ka, UA098.001.074 (Box 74)
    Thesis 1986B consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1986M, 1986P, 1986Q, 1986S, UA098.001.075 (Box 75)
  - Theses, 1986Si, 1986St, 1987Al, 1987B, 1987C, UA098.001.076 (Box 76)
    Thesis 1987B consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1987H, 1987K, 1987N, 1987P, UA098.001.077 (Box 77)
    Thesis 1987N consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1987S, 1987Sa, 1987W, 1988A, 1988Ab, 1988C, UA098.001.078 (Box 78)
  - Theses, 1988Eb, 1988Fe, 1988H, 1988Hu, 1988K, UA098.001.079 (Box 79)
    Thesis1988H consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1988L, 1988M, 1988Re, 1988Sh, UA098.001.080 (Box 80)
    Thesis 1988Sh consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1988Sw, 1988V, 1989Ad, 1989Br, UA098.001.081 (Box 81)
    Thesis 1988Sw consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1989Co, 1989He, 1989Is, 1989Ki, 1989Sa, UA098.001.082 (Box 82)
    Thesis 1989Is consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1989Sw, 1989Wi, 1989Yo, 1990Ag, 1990Ah, UA098.001.083 (Box 83)
    Thesis 1989Wi consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1990Al, 1990Be, 1990Hi, 1990Lu, UA098.001.084 (Box 84)
    1990Be consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1990Pe, 1990Ro, 1990Sa, 1990Su, 1991Ad, UA098.001.085 (Box 85)
    Thesis 1990Pe consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1991Al, 1991Co, 1991Do, 1991Fl, 1991Ge, UA098.001.086 (Box 86)
  - Theses, 1991Ha, 1991Kh, 1991Lo, 1991Ma, UA098.001.087 (Box 87)
    Thesis 1991Kh consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1991Pa, 1991St, 1991Wa, 1992Go, 1992Gr, 1992He, UA098.001.088 (Box 88)
  - Theses, 1992Ho, 1992Li, 1992Ma, 1992Sc, 1992So, UA098.001.089 (Box 89)
  - Theses, 1993Al, 1993An, 1993Ay, 1993Ch, 1993Ch, UA098.001.090 (Box 90)
    Thesis 1993Al consists of two volumes. Theses written by Charles and Chindawongse share the same number, Thesis 1993Ch.
  - Theses, 1993Cl, 1993Dj, 1993Dr, 1993Ha, 1993Ha, UA098.001.091 (Box 91)
    Theses written by Harland and Hayes share the same number, 1993Ha.
  - Theses, 1993Le, 1993Le, 1993Li, 1993Ma, 1993Ma, 1993Ma, 1993Mo, UA098.001.092 (Box 92)
    Theses written by Lehman and Leonard share the same number, 1993Le. Theses written by Magherini, Malbon, Margolies share the same number, 1993Ma.
  - Theses, 1993No, 1993Ro, 1993Sh, 1993Sh, 1993St, 1993Su, UA098.001.093 (Box 93)
    Theses written by Shaw and Sherburne-Benze share the same number, 1993Sh.
  - Theses, 1994Ce, 1994Co, 1994Go, 1994Gr, 1994Gr, 1994Gr, UA098.001.094 (Box 94)
    Theses written by Grandolini, Green and Greenberg share the same number, 1994Gr.
  - Theses, 1994Ha, 1994Ha, 1994Ke, 1994Ki, UA098.001.095 (Box 95)
    Theses written by Haymond and Hays share the same number, 1994Ha.
  - Theses, 1994Li, 1994Li, 1994Ra, 1994Re, 1994Wh, UA098.001.096 (Box 96)
    Thesis 1994Re consists of two volumes. Theses written by Livingstone and Lizano share the same number, 1994Li.
  - Theses, 1995Bh, 1995Br, 1995Ca, 1995En, 1995Fi, 1995In, UA098.001.097 (Box 97)
    Thesis 1995Br consists of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1995Is, 1995Ko, 1995Mi, 1995Mo, 1995Ro, UA098.001.098 (Box 98)
  - Theses,1995Si, 1995Sm, UA098.001.099 (Box 99)
    Thesis 1995Sm consists of three volumes.
  - Theses, 1995Ze, 1996Be, UA098.001.100 (Box 100)
    Theses 1995Ze and 1996Be each consist of two volumes.
  - Theses, 1996Co, 1996Co, 1996De, UA098.001.101 (Box 101)
    Theses written by Cook, consisting of three volumes, and Copeland, consisting of two volumes, share a number, 1996Co.
  - Theses, 1996Du, 1996Ha, 1996Li, 1996Mo, 1996Na, 1996Re, 1996To, UA098.001.102 (Box 102)
  - Theses, 1996Tr, 1996Wi, 1998Ra, 1998Ri, UA098.001.103 (Box 103)
  - Theses, 1998Tu, 1998Wi, 1999Ah, 1999Bo, 1999Ci, 1999Sm, UA098.001.104 (Box 104)
  - Theses, 1999Fa, 1999Jo, 1999Le, 1999Le, 1999Sh, 1999Wa, UA098.001.105 (Box 105)
  - Theses, 2000Ca, 2000Ch, 2000Ha, 2000Li, 2000Ma, 2000Mi, 2000Na, UA098.001.106 (Box 106)
  - Theses, 2000Sa, 2001Ma, 2001Ne, 2001Ro, 2001Sa, 2001Sh, UA098.001.107 (Box 107)
  - Theses, 2001Vo, 2001Wa, 2002Ch, 2002Gl, 2002Ki, 2002Re, 2002Vo, UA098.001.108 (Box 108)
  - Theses, 1999Ru, 2001Hi, 1981Ma, UA098.001.109 (Box 109, 93)
- University Theses and Dissertations, 1894 -- 2013; 1995 -- 2013; UA098.002; 525.6 Linear Feet
  This series contains masters and doctoral theses from circa 1894 to 2008 for all schools except Fletcher School and School of Nutrition. Titles to theses can be found only through the Tufts University Library catalog. Last digits of call number following "LD5391.7 .A2 NO." in Tufts University Library catalog correspond to thesis number in archival record.
  This series is arranged numerically.
  - Theses, 1-21, 1F, 1G, UA098.002.001 (Box 1)
  - Theses, 22-30, [31-32] 33-46, UA098.002.002 (Box 2)
    Copy of Thesis 24 also located in Special Collections under its call number LD5391.7.A2 No. 24; Thesis 31 located in Special Collections under its call number LD59391.7.A2 No. 31 c. 1; Thesis 32 is located in Special Collections under its call number LD5391.7 A2 NO. 32 C. 1
  - Theses, 47, 48, [49] 50-66, UA098.002.003 (Box 3)
    Thesis 49 is located in Special Collections under its call number LD5391.7.A2 NO. 49 c.1 with 16 images of Naragansett Bay Basin and Rock formations
  - Theses, 67-86, UA098.002.004 (Box 4)
  - Theses, 87-107, UA098.002.005 (Box 5)
  - Theses, 108-130, UA098.002.006 (Box 6)
  - Theses, 131-154, UA098.002.007 (Box 7)
  - Theses, 155-177, UA098.002.008 (Box 8)
  - Theses, 178, 180-201, UA098.002.009 (Box 9)
    Thesis #179 is located in the oversize thesis section.
  - Theses, 202-209, 211-225, UA098.002.010 (Box 10)
  - Theses, 226-248, UA098.002.011 (Box 11)
  - Theses, 249-271, UA098.002.012 (Box 12)
  - Theses, 272-294, UA098.002.013 (Box 13)
  - Theses, 295-318, UA098.002.014 (Box 14)
  - Theses, 319-342, UA098.002.015 (Box 15)
  - Theses, 343-370, UA098.002.016 (Box 16)
  - Theses, 371-396, UA098.002.017 (Box 17)
  - Theses, 397-428, UA098.002.018 (Box 18)
  - Theses, 429 - 454, UA098.002.019 (Box 19)
  - Theses, 455-484, UA098.002.020 (Box 20)
  - Theses, 485-510, UA098.002.021 (Box 21)
  - Theses, 511-536, UA098.002.022 (Box 22)
  - Theses, 537-562, UA098.002.023 (Box 23)
  - Theses, 563-583, UA098.002.024 (Box 24)
  - Theses, 584-608, UA098.002.025 (Box 25)
  - Theses, 609-637, UA098.002.026 (Box 26)
  - Theses, 638-661, UA098.002.027 (Box 27)
  - Theses, 662-688, UA098.002.028 (Box 28)
  - Theses, 689-714, UA098.002.029 (Box 29)
  - Theses, 715-737, 730A, UA098.002.030 (Box 30)
  - Theses, 738-764, UA098.002.031 (Box 31)
  - Theses, 765-788, UA098.002.032 (Box 32)
  - Theses, 789-810, UA098.002.033 (Box 33)
  - Theses, 811-832, UA098.002.034 (Box 34)
  - Theses, 833-857, UA098.002.035 (Box 35)
  - Theses, 858-882, UA098.002.036 (Box 36)
  - Theses, 883-904, 905 (Oversize), 906, UA098.002.037 (Box 37)
    Thesis 905 is located in series 003, Oversize University Theses and Dissertations (UA098/003).
  - Theses, 907-925, UA098.002.038 (Box 38)
  - Theses, 926-945, UA098.002.039 (Box 39)
  - Theses, 946-964, UA098.002.040 (Box 40)
  - Theses, 965-983, 983 (Oversize), UA098.002.041 (Box 41)
    Thesis 983 is located in series 003, Oversize University Theses and Dissertations (UA098/003).
  - Theses, 984-1001, UA098.002.042 (Box 42)
  - Theses, 1002-1024, UA098.002.043 (Box 43)
  - Theses, 1025-1047, UA098.002.044 (Box 44)
  - Theses, 1048-1068, UA098.002.045 (Box 45)
  - Theses, 1069-1089, UA098.002.046 (Box 46)
  - Theses, 1090-1108, UA098.002.047 (Box 47)
  - Theses, 1109-1129, UA098.002.048 (Box 48)
  - Theses, 1130-1150, UA098.002.049 (Box 49)
  - Theses, 1151-1170, UA098.002.050 (Box 50)
  - Theses, 1171-1191, UA098.002.051 (Box 51)
  - Theses, 1192-1212, UA098.002.052 (Box 52)
  - Theses, 1213-1233, UA098.002.053 (Box 53)
  - Theses, 1234-1256, UA098.002.054 (Box 54)
  - Theses, 1257-1274, UA098.002.055 (Box 55)
  - Theses, 1275-1293, UA098.002.056 (Box 56)
  - Theses, 1294-1310, UA098.002.057 (Box 57)
  - Theses, 1311-1328, UA098.002.058 (Box 58)
  - Theses, 1329-1347, UA098.002.059 (Box 59)
  - Theses, 1348-1368, UA098.002.060 (Box 60)
  - Theses, 1369-1390, UA098.002.061 (Box 61)
  - Theses, 1391-1408, UA098.002.062 (Box 62)
  - Theses, 1409-1428, UA098.002.063 (Box 63)
  - Theses, 1429-1449, UA098.002.064 (Box 64)